[{
        "question": "What is true about Machine Learning?",
        "option1": "Machine Learning (ML) is that field of computer science",
        "option2": "ML is a type of artificial intelligence that extract patterns out of raw data by using an algorithm or method.",
        "option3": "The main focus of ML is to allow computer systems learn from experience without being explicitly programmed or human intervention.",
        "option4": "All of the above",
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "ML is a field of AI consisting of learning algorithms that?",
        "option1": "Improve their performance",
        "option2": "At executing some task",
        "option3": "Over time with experience",
        "option4": "All of the above",
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "p → 0q is not a?",
        "option1": "hack clause",
        "option2": "horn clause",
        "option3": "structural clause",
        "option4": "system clause",
        "answer": "horn clause"
    },
    {
        "question": "The action _______ of a robot arm specify to Place block A on block B.",
        "option1": "STACK(A,B)",
        "option2": "LIST(A,B)",
        "option3": "QUEUE(A,B)",
        "option4": "ARRAY(A,B)",
        "answer": "STACK(A,B)"
    },
    {
        "question": "A model of language consists of the categories which does not include ________.",
        "option1": "System Unit",
        "option2": "structural units.",
        "option3": "data units",
        "option4": "empirical units",
        "answer": "structural units."
    },
    {
        "question": "The model will be trained with data in one single batch is known as ?",
        "option1": "Batch learning",
        "option2": "Offline learning",
        "option3": "Both A and B",
        "option4": "None of the above",
        "answer": "Both A and B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a widely used and effective machine learning algorithm based on the idea of bagging?",
        "option1": "Decision Tree",
        "option2": "Regression",
        "option3": "Classification",
        "option4": "Random Forest",
        "answer": "Random Forest"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a disadvantage of decision trees?",
        "option1": "Factor analysis",
        "option2": "Decision trees are robust to outliers",
        "option3": "Decision trees are prone to be overfit",
        "option4": "None of the above",
        "answer": "Decision trees are prone to be overfit"
    },
    {
        "question": "How do you handle missing or corrupted data in a dataset?",
        "option1": "Drop missing rows or columns",
        "option2": "Replace missing values with mean/median/mode",
        "option3": "Assign a unique category to missing values",
        "option4": "All of the above",
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "When performing regression or classification, which of the following is the correct way to preprocess the data?",
        "option1": "Normalize the data -> PCA -> training",
        "option2": "PCA -> normalize PCA output -> training",
        "option3": "Normalize the data -> PCA -> normalize PCA output -> training",
        "option4": "None of the above",
        "answer": "Normalize the data -> PCA -> training"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following statements about regularization is not correct?",
        "option1": "Using too large a value of lambda can cause your hypothesis to underfit the data.",
        "option2": "Using too large a value of lambda can cause your hypothesis to overfit the data",
        "option3": "Using a very large value of lambda cannot hurt the performance of your hypothesis.",
        "option4": "None of the above",
        "answer": "None of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which of the following cases will K-means clustering fail to give good results?",
        "option1": "Data points with outliers",
        "option2": "Data points with different densities",
        "option3": "Data points with nonconvex shapes",
        "option4": "All of the above",
        "answer": "All of the above"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a reasonable way to select the number of principal components 'k'?",
        "option1": "Choose k to be the smallest value so that at least 99% of the varinace is retained.",
        "option2": "Choose k to be 99% of m (k = 0.99*m, rounded to the nearest integer).",
        "option3": "Choose k to be the largest value so that 99% of the variance is retained.",
        "option4": "Use the elbow method.",
        "answer": "Choose k to be the smallest value so that at least 99% of the varinace is retained."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is a sentence parser typically used for?",
        "option1": "It is used to parse sentences to check if they are utf-8 compliant.",
        "option2": "It is used to parse sentences to derive their most likely syntax tree structures.",
        "option3": "It is used to parse sentences to assign POS tags to all tokens.",
        "option4": "It is used to check if sentences can be parsed into meaningful tokens.",
        "answer": "It is used to parse sentences to derive their most likely syntax tree structures."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a subset of machine learning?",
        "option1": "Numpy",
        "option2": "SciPy",
        "option3": "Deep Learning",
        "option4": "All of the above",
        "answer": "Deep Learning"
    },
    {
        "question": "RNNs stands for?",
        "option1": "Receives neural networks",
        "option2": "Report neural networks",
        "option3": "Recording neural networks",
        "option4": "Recurrent neural networks",
        "answer": "Recurrent neural networks"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many layers Deep learning algorithms are constructed?",
        "option1": "2",
        "option2": "3",
        "option3": "4",
        "option4": "5",
        "answer": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is well suited for perceptual tasks?",
        "option1": "Feed-forward neural networks",
        "option2": "Recurrent neural networks",
        "option3": "Convolutional neural networks",
        "option4": "Reinforcement Learning",
        "answer": "Convolutional neural networks"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is/are Limitations of deep learning?",
        "option1": "Data labeling",
        "option2": "Obtain huge training datasets",
        "option3": "Both A and B",
        "option4": "None of the above",
        "answer": "Both A and B"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following statements is true when you use 1×1 convolutions in a CNN?",
        "option1": "It can help in dimensionality reduction",
        "option2": "It can be used for feature pooling",
        "option3": "It suffers less overfitting due to small kernel size",
        "option4": "All of the above",
        "answer": "All of the above"
    }
]